<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:foaf="http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/" xmlns:og="http://ogp.me/ns#" xmlns:rdfs="http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#" xmlns:schema="http://schema.org/" xmlns:sioc="http://rdfs.org/sioc/ns#" xmlns:sioct="http://rdfs.org/sioc/types#" xmlns:skos="http://www.w3.org/2004/02/skos/core#" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema#" version="2.0" xml:base="https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en">
  <channel>
    <title>ECDC - RSS - COVID-19</title>
    <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    
    <item>
  <title>Data for the maps in support of the Council Recommendation on a coordinated approach to the restriction of free movement in response to the COVID-19 pandemic in the EU/EEA and the UK</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/indicators-maps-support-council-recommendation</link>
  <description>The downloadable data file contains the data on which the maps requested in the Council Recommendation on a coordinated approach to the restriction of free movement in response to the COVID-19 pandemic in EU/EEA and the UK are based. They are published every Thursday.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/indicators-maps-support-council-recommendation</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Data on the weekly subnational 14-day notification rate of new COVID-19 cases</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/weekly-subnational-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</link>
  <description>The downloadable data file contains information on the 14-day notification rate of new cases per 100 000 inhabitants for COVID-19 by day and subnational region. Each row contains the corresponding data for a certain epidemiological week and per subnational region. The file is updated weekly. You may use the data in line with ECDC’s copyright policy.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/weekly-subnational-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Data on the daily subnational 14-day notification rate of new COVID-19 cases</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/subnational-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</link>
  <description>The downloadable data file contains information on the 14-day notification rate of new cases per 100 000 inhabitants for COVID-19 by day and subnational region. Each row contains the corresponding data for a certain day and per subnational region. The file is updated weekly. You may use the data in line with ECDC’s copyright policy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;br /&gt;
The source is either TESSy COVID-19, subnational daily data, or an official Github source, or an official website.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/subnational-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Data on 14-day notification rate of new COVID-19 cases and deaths</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/data-national-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</link>
  <description>These files contain data on the 14-day notification rate of newly reported COVID-19 cases per 100 000 population and 14-day notification rate of reported deaths per million population by day and country, in EU/EEA and the UK. Each row contains the corresponding data for a certain day and per country. The files are updated weekly. You may use the data in accordance to ECDC’s copyright policy.&lt;br /&gt;</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/data-national-14-day-notification-rate-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Data on hospital and ICU admission rates and current occupancy for COVID-19 </title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/download-data-hospital-and-icu-admission-rates-and-current-occupancy-covid-19</link>
  <description>The downloadable data files contain information about hospitalisation and Intensive Care Unit (ICU) admission rates and current occupancy for COVID-19 by date and country. Each row contains the corresponding data for a certain date (day or week) and per country. The file is updated weekly. You may use the data in line with ECDC’s copyright policy.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/download-data-hospital-and-icu-admission-rates-and-current-occupancy-covid-19</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Data on testing for COVID-19 by week and country</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/covid-19-testing</link>
  <description>The downloadable data file contains information about testing volume for COVID-19 by week and country. Each row contains the corresponding data for a country and a week. The file is updated weekly. You may use the data in line with ECDC’s copyright policy.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/covid-19-testing</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Coronavirus disease 2019 (COVID-19) and supply of substances of human origin in the EU/EEA - Second update</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19-and-supply-substances-human-origin</link>
  <description>This second update of the original document integrates the experience of maintaining safe and sufficient supply of substances of human origin (SoHO) gained in the course of the COVID-19 pandemic and through recent scientific developments in understanding the evolution of the disease.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/coronavirus-disease-2019-covid-19-and-supply-substances-human-origin</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Download the daily number of new reported cases of COVID-19 by country worldwide</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/download-todays-data-geographic-distribution-covid-19-cases-worldwide</link>
  <description>The downloadable data file is updated daily and contains the latest available public data on COVID-19. You may use the data in line with ECDC’s copyright policy.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/download-todays-data-geographic-distribution-covid-19-cases-worldwide</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Infographic: Preventing COVID-19 transmission during the festive season</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/infographic-making-festive-season-safer</link>
  <description>Holidays are important, but your health and that of your loved ones, especially those that are more vulnerable, should come first during this period. This infographic offers advice on how to make the holidays safer. </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/infographic-making-festive-season-safer</guid>
    </item>
<item>
  <title>Communicable disease threats report, 29 November-5 December 2020, week 49</title>
  <link>https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/communicable-disease-threats-report-29-november-5-december-2020-week-49</link>
  <description>The ECDC Communicable Disease Threats Report (CDTR) is a weekly bulletin for epidemiologists and health professionals on active public health threats. This issue covers the period 29 November-5 December 2020 and includes updates on COVID-19, Legionnaires' disease, polio, seasonal influenza and Middle East respiratory syndrome coronavirus (MERS-CoV).</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 13:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>ECDC</dc:creator>
    <guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.ecdc.europa.eu/en/publications-data/communicable-disease-threats-report-29-november-5-december-2020-week-49</guid>
    </item>

  </channel>
</rss>